LEONARDO O'MEARA

Systems Engineer | Software Developer

- +57 (310) 266-7910
- Bogotá, Colombia
- Leonardogarzon32@outlook.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/leonardoomeara
- github.com/LeonardoOmeara

EDUCATION

Systems and telecommunications Degree

Sergio Arboleda University 2017 – 2022

SKILLS

- HTML / CSS / JavaScript
- Python
- Java
- SOL
- ReactJS
- Git

LANGUAGES

English

C1 Level Certificated by Sergio Arboleda university

PROFILE

Systems Engineer with 1 year of experience working as a freelancer building websites for two clients and half a year working with Python and the A360 API at Stanley Black & Decker. I have knowledge in different programming languages such as JavaScript and Python along with the use of GIT and NextJS as development framework.

I have initiative to solve problems, the ability to learn new technologies quickly, very good team work abilities and the willingness to learn day by day.

EXPERIENCE

July 2021 - October 2021

Web Developer Short Film "Escondite para dos"

- Develop a responsive website dedicated to the crowdfunding of the short film.
- Manage and upload the website to a hosting service.
- Adapt the initial design and make it responsive.
 HTML / CSS / JS / Responsive Design



January 2022 – July 2022

Automation Intern Stanley Black & Decker

- Create a Python Script to extract information from the A360 API.
- Create a Power BI report, connect it to the script and transform the data to identify bots that were not running as they should.

Python / A360 API / Postman / Power BI

RELEVANT PROJECTS

- "Escondite para dos" Website (HTML, CSS, JS, Responsive Design)
 https://leonardoomeara.github.io/EsconditeParaDos/
- Batabit (HTML, CSS, Responsive Design)
 https://leonardoomeara.github.io/Batatabit/
- Real State Web App (NextJS, RapidAPI) In progress

IMPORTANT ACHIEVEMENT

"Ser pilo paga" Scholarship winner in 2016.